

CONTACT

M

Noorhanburhan@gmail.com



+964 7802473024



Baghdad, Hay al Adel



Norhan-Burhan-3b75694538

SKILL

Management Skills

Computer Skills

Communication Skills

Microsoft Office

LANGUAGES

English

Arabic

Truky

HOBBIES









Noorhan Burhan Adhem

Translator and HR assistant

ABOUT ME

My name is Norhan, I am 30 years old, I graduated from Al Turath University college in 2015, I live in Baghdad, I worked before as a Reservations Agent and Translator in Al Yaqeen company and Human Resources Assistant with Al Dirwas Al Arabi Ltd. company, I am hard worker ready to take on challenging,

EDUCATION

2011-2015 English Department

Al Turath University College

WORK EXPERIENCE

2015-2017 Reservations Agent and Translator Al Yaqeen company

- *Assisting and advising customers who may be choosing from a variety of travel options.
- *Making reservations for customers based on their various requirements and budgetary allowances.
- *Checking the availability of accommodation or transportation on the customers' desired travel dates.
- *Helping plan travel itineraries by suggesting local tourist attractions and places of interest.
- *Processing payments and sending confirmation details to customers.
- *Sorting out any issues that may arise with bookings or reservations.
 *Selling and promoting reservation services.
- *Answering any questions customers might have about the reservation process.
- *Up-selling, when appropriate, by informing customers of additional services or speciapackages, such as tour tickets, travel insurance, or upgraded seats/accommodations.
- *Providing support to customers who may need to amend or cancel a reservation.
- *Reading material and researching industry-specific .
- *Converting text and audio recordings in one language to one or more others.
- *Ensuring translated texts conveys original meaning and tone.

2017-2020 Human Resources Assistant Al Dirwas Al Arabi

- *Compile and update employee records (hard and soft copies)
- *Coordinate communication with candidates and schedule interviews
- *Conduct initial orientation to newly hired employees
- *Compiling reports and spreadsheets and preparing spreadsheets
- *Answering employee questions
- *Preparing new employee files
- *Researching a employees references and academic qualifications
- *Reading all correspondence including inquiry letters, job applications and CVs that are sent in